Caffè Lena collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 7: Dick Kavanaugh collection
    - Sub-subseries 1: Music
      - Utah Phillips (2 of 2), November 24, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR201)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0003. Side B is blank.
      - Utah Phillips (1 of 2), November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR203)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0005.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 1 of 8): Eleanor Reynolds (with Camille West), Rick Kunz, Michael Burns, George Drew, Dave Utter, Dick Kavanaugh, Marika Higgins, Andy Jenson, November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR105)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0001.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 2 of 8): Blind Lemon Joy, Camille West, Rick Kunz, Terri and Maria, Addie and Olin, November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR106)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0002.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 3 of 8), November 26, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.; 9 min. recorded): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR107)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0003. Side B is blank.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 4 of 8): Dave Van Ronk, Rosalie Sorrels, Spalding Gray, November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR108)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0004.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 5 of 8), November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR109)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0005.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 6 of 8): Margaret MacArthur, Jack Landron [?], Christine Lavin, Michael Kuni [?], November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR110)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0006.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 7 of 8), November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR111)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0007.
      - Memorial tribute to Lena (part 8 of 8): Addie and Olin, Steve Kovacik, Dick Kavanaugh, Terri Roben and Maria, Erica [?], November 26, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR112)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0008.
      - Josh White, Jr. at Caffè Lena, December 15, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR299)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0044.
      - Lena Spencer leaving a message on an answering machine (dub), circa 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.; 1 min 30 sec.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR125)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0001. Side B is blank.
      - Press release Lena, 1989 or 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR126)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0002. Side B is blank.
      - Fete Des Trois Roi live at Caffè Lena, January 12, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR268)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0013.
      - Suburban Mothers From Hell (Eleanor Reynolds and Camille West), January 14, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR245)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0047.
      - Bill Staines live at Caffè Lena, January 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR300)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0045.
      - John Gorka at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), January 27, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR310)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0055.
      - John Gorka at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), January 27, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR309)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0054.
      - Bill Morrissey live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), January 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR282)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0027. Part 1 of 2 is missing. Side B is blank.
      - Adirondack Fiddlers Night (1 of 2), February 2, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR225)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0027.
      - Adirondack Fiddlers Night (2 of 2), February 2, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR226)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0028. Side B is blank.
      - Brooks Williams (1 of 2), 32907, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR212)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0014.
      - Brooks Williams (2 of 2), February 3, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR213)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0015. Side B is blank.
      - Betsy, Steve Frye, and Howard Jack (children's concert), February 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR232)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0034.
      - Schooner Fare (1 of 2), February 17, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR234)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0036.
      - Schooner Fare (2 of 2), February 17, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR233)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0035.
      - Not Necessarily the Blues: Jeff Gonzales, John Ragusa (1 of 2), February 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR244)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0046.
      - Not Necessarily the Blues: Jeff Gonzales, John Ragusa (2 of 2), February 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR243)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0045.
      - Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), March 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR291)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0036.
      - Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), March 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR290)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0035.
      - Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen live at Caffè Lena (1 of 1), March 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR292)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0037.
      - Critton Hollow String Band, March 10, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR194)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0051.
      - Dyer Switch (1 of 2), March 23, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR235)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0037.
      - Dyer Switch (2 of 2), March 23, 1990, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR236)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0038.
      - Cathy Winter and Jamie Morton (1 of 2), March 30, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR223)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0025.
      - Cathy Winter (2 of 2), March 30, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR224)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0026.
      - Huxtable, Christensen and Hood (1 of 2), April 6, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR238)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0040.
      - Huxtable, Christensen and Hood (2 of 2), April 6, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR237)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0039. Side B is blank.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 1, May 18, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR246)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0049.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 2: Kevin Gavitt, Kate Sontag, Dave Hitt, Dave Elder, The Funky Peas, Marty Hues [?], unannounced author, The Spores (Dotty, Peter, Ryke), May 18, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR247)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0050.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 3: Chris Jeffers, Andy Jensen, Mike Jerline and Tony Markellis, Kingsly and McGeouch, David Buran, May 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR248)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0051.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 4: Dick Kavanaugh, Short of Breath, Tom Glee, (solo and with Erica), Mark Overhull, Dan and unidentified person, May 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR249)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0052.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 5: Ken Gaines and George, Terri and Maria, Dave Utter, May 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR250)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0053.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 6: Chris Gallagher, Camille West, Skip Penk, Ken Gaines, May 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR251)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0054.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 7: Tony Markellis, Ed Lauman, Vicky LaVictoria, and Don Armstrong; Chester, Ed Hewitt, Emilio [last name not given], The Embryonic Journey, May 20, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR252)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0055.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 8: George Ward, Paul Mercer, Camille West, Steve Kovacik, May 20, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR253)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0056.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 9: Peter O'Toole, Paul Straussman, Ford Diz [?], David Colburn, May 20, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR254)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0057.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 10: Ann Bailey, Dave Debonzo, Ed Baginar [?], Jim Gaudet, May 20, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR255)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0058.
      - 30th Anniversary: Caffè Annual Folk-A-Thon, part 11: Jim Gorvay [?], Whoopee Jazz (Addie, Olin and Peter), May 20, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR239)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0041.
      - Broken String Band, September 9, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR209)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0011.
      - Cosy Sheridan, January 20, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR161)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0018. Side B is blank.
      - Patrick Ball, March 8, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR285)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0030.
      - Claudia Schmidt, March 24, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR160)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0017.
      - Walt Michael and company (1 of 2), April 13, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR171)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0028. Named as Walt Michaels in the documentation.
      - Walt Michael and company, plus an unannounced band (2 of 2), April 13, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR172)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0029. See note for SR172.
      - Joan Crane, Frank Orsini (1 of 2), April 14, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR154)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0011.
      - Joan Crane, Frank Orsini (2 of 2), April 14, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR153)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0010.
      - Kathy Lee Johnson and Jeff Wilkinson, April 20, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR157)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0014.
      - Jane Gillman and Kim M'Carver [sic], April 28, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR192)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0049. Kim also goes by the name Kimberly.
      - Alan Block and George Wilson, May 3, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR170)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0027
      - Anson Olds, May 3, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR193)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0050. Side B is blank.
      - Carla Sciaky, May 10, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR177)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0034.
      - Peter Rowan, May 12, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR322)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0008.
      - Josephine, May 23, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR197)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0054.
      - John McCutcheon (1 of 2), June 2, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR190)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0047.
      - John McCutcheon (2 of 2), June 2, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR191)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0048. Side B is blank.
      - Judy Poland, July 6, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR152)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0009.
      - Lynn Hardy, July 6, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR156)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0013.
      - Jim Gaudet, August 3, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR176)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0033.
      - Tom Chapin (1 of 2), August 4, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR278)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0023. Michael Mark on bass, John Cobert on piano.
      - Tom Chapin (2 of 2), August 4, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR279)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0024.
      - The O'Tones, Woopie Jazz (1 of 2), August 23, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR149)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0006.
      - The O'Tones (2 of 2), August 23, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR150)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0007.
      - Ghosthouse's open house at Lena's, August 30, 1991, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR151)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0008.
      - John Herald and Frank Wakefield (1 of 2), September 21, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR320)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0006.
      - John Herald and Frank Wakefield (2 of 2), September 21, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR321)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0007. Side A is blank.
      - Diane Diachsihin (1 of 2), December 8, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR158)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0015.
      - Diane Diachsihin (2 of 2), December 8, 1991, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR159)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0016. Side B is blank.
      - Terri Roben and Marie, December 15, 1991, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR175)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0032.
      - David Roth (1 of 2), July 10, 1992, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR241)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0043.
      - David Roth (2 of 2), July 10, 1992, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR242)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0044. Side B is blank.
      - Frank Wakefield and the Bear Bridge Band (1 of 2), July 27, 1992, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR148)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0005.
      - Frank Wakefield (2 of 2), July 27, 1992, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR147)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0004. Side B is blank.
      - Bruce Pratt, October 11, 1992, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR155)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0012.
      - Ramblin' Jack Elliott, October 11, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR323)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0009.
      - Blues Alley, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR367)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0054. Side A has only one song. Side B is blank.
      - Margaret MacArthur, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR188)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0045. The tape comes from Dave Utter. SR188 and SR189 are probably parts 1 and 2 of the same concert)
      - Margaret MacArthur, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR189)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0046. Side B is blank. See note for SR188.
    - Sub-subseries 2: Board meetings
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), January 14, 1990 (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR114)
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), January 14, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR115)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0011. Side B is blank.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), January 28, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR116)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0012.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), January 28, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR117)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0013.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), February 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR118)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0014.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), February 3, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR119)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0015.
      - Board meetings (1 of 3), February 12, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR120)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0016.
      - Board meetings (2 of 3), February 12, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR121)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0017. Side B is blank.
      - Board meetings (3 of 3), February 12, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR122)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0018.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), February 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR124)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0020.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), February 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR123)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0019.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), February 26, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR130)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0006.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), February 26, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR131)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0007.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), March 5, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR132)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0008.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), March 5, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR133)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0009.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), March 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR134)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0010.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), March 19, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR135)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0011.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), April 1, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR136)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0012.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), April 1, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR137)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0013.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), April 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR138)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0014.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), April 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR139)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0015.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), May 1, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR140)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0016.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), May 1, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR141)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0017.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), May 22, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR143)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0019.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), May 22, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR142)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0018. Side B is blank.
      - Board meetings (1 of 2), July 10, 1990, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR129)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0005.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), July 10, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR127)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0003. Side B is blank. Both SR127 and SR128 are designated part 2 of 2.
      - Board meetings (2 of 2), July 10, 1990, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR128)
        Original item ID: DK B2 0004. Side B is blank. See note for SR127.
  - Subseries 8: ZBS Media collection
    Includes Robert Durand's "Caffè Lena Show," and Bob Bielecki unedited tapes.
    - Gordon Bok and Annie Muir, possibly December 1973 (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR422)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0008. Annie Muir also goes by the name Ann Mayo Muir.
    - Will Spires and Jane Voss, January 14, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR423)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0009.
    - Kenny Hall, February 3, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR415)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0001.
    - Kenny Hall, February 7, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR416)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0002.
    - Don McLean and Frank Wakefield, Logan English, March 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR426)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0012. Lena Spencer also sings.
    - Frank Wakefield and friends, April 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track or quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR425)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0011.
    - Paul Geremia, June 14, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR429)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0015.
    - Rosalie Sorrels, May 24, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR428)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0014.
    - Rosalie Sorrels, May 26, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR421)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0007.
    - Sleepy John Estes with Hammie Nixon, June 21, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR427)
      Original item ID: BB ZBS B10 0013.
    - Sleepy John Estes and Hammie Nixon, June 27, 1974, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 10 in. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR432)